<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutoring on Sarah Helmbrecht</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tutoring/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutoring on Sarah Helmbrecht</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tutoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutoring/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutoring/about/</guid>
      <description>I graduated from Anderson High School in Austin, Texas in May 2020 with an International Baccalaureate Certificate and Distinguished Achievement. I scored a 1580 on the SAT (790 math, 790 verbal) in one try with no tutoring or prep courses. I also earned two AP Scholar Awards with Distinction and a National AP Scholar Award for my successes on 12 different AP tests. Next, I attended Tulane University in New Orleans, Louisiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calculus 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutoring/calculus1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutoring/calculus1/</guid>
      <description>Precalculus Review Limits Derivatives Inverse Functions L&amp;rsquo;Hôpital&amp;rsquo;s Rule Applications of Differentiation </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutoring/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutoring/contact/</guid>
      <description> Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutoring/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutoring/services/</guid>
      <description>I offer a free 30 minute virtual consultation to discuss your needs and goals, as well as the tutoring process itself.&#xA;I am available to tutor in-person in Austin, as well as virtually. Both in-person and virtual sessions have a minimum length of 1 hour. For virtual sessions, I ask that students be prepared to either screen share while they write on a tablet or set up a camera above their paper so that I can see their work; this is necessary for making virtual sessions interactive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
